# **Shreya Bakharel**

(513) 537-7230 | shreya.bakharel@gmail.com | El Cerrito, California https://www.linkedin.com/in/shreya-bakharel/

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Detail-oriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications as well as programming skills necessary to become a developer. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS & CERTIFICATION**

**W3Schools JavaScript Certification** 

Java
Spring Data JPA
Unit Testing

JavaScript
Spring Security (JWT)
SOLID OOP Principles

HTML
Bootstrap
Dependencies Injection

• CSS • REST API's • Git

• SpringBoot • SQL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

ChooseU (formerly Generation USA) Full Stack Java Developer Program | Remote | 03/2023-07/2023 Training Participant

- Participated in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasized hands-on practical application
- Learning and deploying the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Implementing basic unit tests and deploying the application.

#### Eureka Restaurant | Berkeley, California | 12//2022 - Current

Server

- Demonstrated exceptional multitasking abilities in a fast-paced restaurant environment, efficiently managing various tasks including taking orders, serving food, and processing payments.
- Utilized strong communication skills to interact with customers, understanding their needs and effectively relaying information to the kitchen and bar staff.
- Showcased adaptability and problem-solving skills in handling unexpected challenges, such as addressing customer complaints, accommodating special dietary requirements, and managing high customer demand.

#### Amazon Fulfillment Center | Monroe, Ohio | 05/2022 - 11/2022

Amazon Associate

- Used handheld computers to enter data quickly and accurately into the system
- Completed all assigned tasks in a timely fashion to meet productivity goals
- Assisted team members in the completion of departmental objectives to maximize workflow

### Stonestep AG | Kathmandu, Nepal | 03/2018 - 11/2021

Claims Adjuster

- Analyzed claims and collaborated with hospitals and clinics to validate claim information
- Developed comprehensive program documents, including scripts, policy wording, and reporting formats, as well as drafted business proposals and contracts, and created UI/UX samples
- Maintained data and document files for programs and projects, and provided essential logistical and administrative support to team members
- Oversaw social media accounts and promotional activities

## **EDUCATION**

Rajiv Gandhi University of Health Sciences | Bangalore, India | (07/ 2017)

Bachelor in Pharmacy. Graduated with distinction